# Will Polliard



### **About Me**

I'm a continuous learner who loves using the latest digital tools to help businesses achieve their marketing and sales goals.

I've worked with companies across the United States and beyond to generate and sustain Inbound Marketing success. I'm currently most fascinated with UX-centric website design and the importance of user intent in SEO.

When I'm away from the office I enjoy learning new things (currently working on JavaScript and jQuery), spending time outdoors, sipping a good cup of coffee and spending time with family.

### **Let's Connect**

T: 352-263-5563

wpolliard@gmail.com www.willpolliard.com

Tampa Bay Area Florida



#### **Experience**

## Inbound Marketing Consultant Bluleadz Inbound Marketing / Tampa, FL

Apr 2015 - Present

Responsible for creating and executing inbound marketing strategies that help clients achieve their unique business goals. Direct point of contact for portfolio of clients and accountable for facilitating weekly meetings to review account growth and client satisfaction. Coordinate with internal and external teams to keep projects on-time and focused on results. Currently responsible for four accounts totaling over \$22,000 in monthly recurring revenue. Also provides weekly paid media management for a fifth account and is the Product Owner for seven-member Scrum team.

## Account Executive Total Quality Logistics / Tampa, FL

Nov 2014 - Apr 2015

Generated leads via cold calling and nurtured them into customers. Developed tailored logistics solutions for client's including Publix and Tropicana while maintaining strict deadlines. Acted as a liason between shippers, receivers and other supply chain participants. Ensured superior customer experience.

## Deputy Sheriff Citrus County Sheriff's Office / Crystal River, FL

Jul 2013 - Nov 2014

Initiated patrols to preserve public tranquility and prevent/discover the commission of crime. Conducted detailed criminal investigations. Performed lawful arrests and developed case reports for use as court testimony. Gathered intelligence through self-initiated surveillance patrols which was communicated to task units for further investigation. Maintained favorable image of the agency.



#### **Education**

2010 - 2014

University of South Florida B.S. Marketing / Tampa, FL



#### **Skills**

Hubspot Software	Inbound Strategy	Marketing Automation
Email Marketing	Website Optimization	Agile / Scrum
SEO	Content Marketing	Social Media Marketing
AdWords & FB Ads	Google Analytics	HTML & CSS